let questions = [
  {
    question: "Commonly used data types DO NOT include:",
    choices: ["strings", "booleans", "alerts", "numbers"],
    answer: "alerts"
  },

  {
    question:
      "The condition in an if / else statement is enclosed within ____.",
    choices: ["quotes", "curly brackets", "parentheses", "square brackets"],
    answer: "parentheses"
  },

  {
    question: "Why do JavaScript and Java have similar name?",
    choices: [
      "JavaScript is a stripped-down version of Java",
      "JavaScript's syntax is loosely based on Java's",
      "They both originated on the island of Java",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    answer: "JavaScript's syntax is loosely based on Java's"
  },

  {
    question:
      "When a user views a page containing a JavaScript program, which machine actually executes the script?",
    choices: [
      "The User's machine running a Web browser",
      "The Web server",
      "A central machine deep within Netscape's corporate offices",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    answer: "The User's machine running a Web browser"
  },

  {
    question: "______ JavaScript is also called client-side JavaScript",
    choices: ["Microsoft", "Navigator", "LiveWire", "Native"],
    answer: "Navigator"
  },

  {
    question: " __________ JavaScript is also called server-side JavaScript",
    choices: ["Microsoft", "Navigator", "LiveWire", "Native"],
    answer: "LiveWire"
  },

  {
    question: "What are variables used for in JavaScript Programs?",
    choices: [
      "Storing numbers, dates, or other values",
      "Varying randomly",
      "Causing high-school algebra flashbacks",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    answer: "Storing numbers, dates, or other values"
  },

  {
    question:
      "_____ JavaScript statements embedded in an HTML page can respond to user events such as mouse-clicks, form input, and page navigation.",
    choices: ["Client-side", "Server-side", "Local", "Native"],
    answer: "Client-side"
  },

  {
    question:
      "______ tag is an extension to HTML that can enclose any number of JavaScript statements.",
    choices: ["Script>", "Body", "Head", "Title"],
    answer: "Script"
  },

  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid JavaScript variable name?",
    choices: [
      "2names",
      "_first_and_last_names",
      "FirstAndLast",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    answer: "2names"
  },

  {
    question: 'What is the correct JavaScript syntax to write "Hello World"?',
    choices: [
      'System.out.println("Hello World")',
      'println ("Hello World")',
      'document.write("Hello World")',
      'response.write("Hello World")'
    ],
    answer: 'document.write("Hello World")'
  },

  {
    question:
      'What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called " abc.js"?',
    choices: [
      '<script href=" abc.js">',
      '<script name=" abc.js">',
      '<script src=" abc.js">',
      "None of the above"
    ],
    answer: '<script src=" abc.js">'
  },

  {
    question: "What does the <noscript> tag do?",
    choices: [
      "Enclose text to be displayed by non-JavaScript browsers.",
      "Prevents scripts on the page from executing.",
      "Describes certain low-budget movies.",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    answer: "Enclose text to be displayed by non-JavaScript browsers."
  },

  {
    question:
      "If para1 is the DOM object for a paragraph, what is the correct syntax to change the text within the paragraph?",
    choices: [
      '"New Text"?',
      'para1.value="New Text";',
      'para1.firstChild.nodeValue= "New Text";',
      'para1.nodeValue="New Text";'
    ],
    answer: 'para1.value="New Text";'
  },

  {
    question: "JavaScript entities start with _______ and end with _________.",
    choices: [
      "Semicolon, colon",
      "Semicolon, Ampersand",
      "Ampersand, colon",
      "Ampersand, semicolon"
    ],
    answer: "Ampersand, semicolon"
  },

  {
    question: "Which of the following best describes JavaScript?",
    choices: [
      "a low-level programming language.",
      "a scripting language precompiled in the browser.",
      "a compiled scripting language.",
      "an object-oriented scripting language."
    ],
    answer: "an object-oriented scripting language."
  }
];
